啊～哈哈,啊～哈哈
♪ Aah haa haa, aah haa haa ♪
啊～哈哈～哈哈～哈哈
♪ Aah haa haa haa haa haa haa ♪
啊～哈哈,啊～哈哈
♪ Aah haa haa, aah haa haa ♪
啊～哈哈～哈哈～哈哈～哈～哈～～
♪ Aah haa haa haa haa haa haa haa haaaaaa ♪
你为何要在此停留?
♪ Why would you want to be here? ♪
在这能看到什么?
♪ What do you ever see here?
这岂不让你更加悲伤?
♪ That doesn't make you feel worse than you do? ♪
请说,情感用处是何,蓝?
♪ And tell me, what's the use of feeling, Blue? ♪
为何你想雇佣那些
♪ Why would you want to employ her♪
毁灭她的遗物?
♪ subjects that destroyed her?
何苦维护动物园?
♪ Why keep up her silly zoo?
哦,请说
♪ Oh, tell me
情感用处是何,蓝?
♪ What's the use of feeling, Blue? ♪
军队有用处,能进行一场战争
♪ An army has a use, they can go and fight a war ♪
蓝宝石有用处,她可以见时知己
♪ A Sapphire has a use, she can tell you what it's for ♪
蓝玛瑙能慑人,青金石能塑星
♪ An Agate terrifies, a Lapis terraforms ♪
当她们需要钻石时你在哪,蓝?
♪ Where's their Diamond when they need her, Blue? ♪
你必须要挺起胸来,蓝
♪ You've got to be a leader, Blue ♪
对,当然,我们还爱她
♪ Yes, of course, we still love her ♪
而且永不会忘记她
♪ And we're always thinking of her ♪
但空是怀念没有用
♪ But now there's nothing we can do ♪
那请说
♪ So tell me
情感用处是何?
♪ What's the use of feeling? ♪
情感用处是何,蓝?
♪ What's the use of feeling, Blue? ♪
哦
♪ Ohh
你怎能做到面对这里
♪ How can you stand to be here with it all? ♪
面对这里
♪ Here with it all
被自己的悔恨淹没?
♪ Drowning in all this regret?
忘记她不是更好吗?
♪ Wouldn't you rather forget her? ♪
哦～哦
♪ Ohhh
难道不更应抛下过去?
♪ Won't it be grand to get rid of it all? ♪
抛下过去
♪ Rid of it all
让我们准备进攻
♪ Let's make a plan of attack
停止回首然后展望未来
♪ Start looking forward and stop looking back ♪
哦
♪ Oh
对,当然,我们还爱着她
♪ yes, of course, we still love her
而且永不会忘记她
♪ And we're always thinking of her ♪
我其实也在想着她
♪ Don't you know I miss her, too? ♪
但请说
♪ But tell me
感情用处是何?
♪ What's the use of feeling? ♪
嗯～哼哼,嗯～哼哼
♪ Hmm hmm hmm, hmm hmm hmm
嗯～哼哼～哼哼～哼哼～哼～哼～～
♪ Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmmmmm ♪